Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Development, Records SC0319
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2007-025
  - Centennial Campaign Files
    - Campaign—Communications 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lucite Blocks Costs (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lucite Blocks Bids (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Centennial—Speech File (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Donor Recognition (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Centennial Grove (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Endowed Professorships Publications (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Keystone Program (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Campaign History (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Centennial Campaign Budgets (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - NCC San Francisco (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - SF NCC (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco NCC Guests (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - SF NCC (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Dinner Misc. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - SF NCC (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - National Centennial Celebrations Post-San Francisco Task Forces (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - SF NCC (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - San Francisco NCC (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - SF NCC (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Portland NCC Dinner Committee (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - NCC—Portland (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - NCC—Portland (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Seattle NCC Friday Misc. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Seattle NCC Saturday & General (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Seattle NCC (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - San Diego NCC (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Portland—NCC (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Portland NCC 5/5-5/6 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - General Information/FYI (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Assignments (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - NCC—Chicago (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - NCC—Orange Co. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - NCC/Orange County (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Phoenix NCC (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Phoenix & Texas NCCs (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - SJ NCC (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - SJNCC Honorees (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - SJ NCC (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - San Jose NCC (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - SJ NCC (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - SJNCC Invitations (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Directories (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - SJNCC—Speakers (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - SJNCC—General (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Invitation List (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - San Jose 12/10-11/89 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - NCC San Jose (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - San Jose NCC (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - LA Budget (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - NCC Portland (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - NY Friday Invitations/Friday Misc. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Co-Chairs/Dinner Committee NY NCC (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - NY NCC Donor List (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - NY NCC Saturday & General (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - New York NCC Attendance Reports (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - New York National Centennial Celebration April 22-23, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - NCC—New York (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Bob Woods (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Campaign Public Announcement Events February 10, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Campaign Regional Campaign Events (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Campaign Second Anniversary Regional Campaign Events Committee (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Cornerstone and the Co-Chairs (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cornerstone Week (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Celebration, November 10-11 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Cornerstone Week (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Cornerstone Week (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Weekend (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Finale Weekend (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Cornerstone Week May 14-16, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Campaign: Cornerstone Week (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Cornerstone Weekend (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Info (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Celebrations Planning ‘86 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Centennial Celebration Planning 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Centennial Pins (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Finale Weekend Publications (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - CCOC— Centennial Celebration Operating Committee #4 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Centennial Finale (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Press Coverage (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - David Fulten (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Celebration Planning 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Press Coverage (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cornerstone Week 5/87 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Campaign/Volunteer Notebook (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Newsletter (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Campaign Volunteer Chart (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Centennial 100 Project (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chairs Meetings (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - South Bay Council Meeting September 29, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Working Session—1/26 and 2/16/89 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Peninsula Working Session—3/8/89 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - First Working Session April 6, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Agenda—Peninsula Region April 13, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - SB Council Assignments (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Major Gift Co-Chairs (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - October 12, 1988 National Major Gifts Co-Chairs Meeting—Room 136, GSB Bldg. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - 10/31/91 CC Steering Cttee Freidenrich Regional Review (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Roy Anderson Reg Review 12/5/90 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Sept '88 Reg. Reviews (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Major Gifts Co-Chairs Meeting 12/11/90 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Cttee 10/12/89 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - MG CoChairs mtg 6/14/90 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chairs (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - May 8, 1986—Campaign Steering Committee Meeting 2:00-5:00 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Vice Chair Call Sheets (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee May 23, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Feb. 14, 1989 Major Gifts Co-Chairs Mtg Dean's Conference Room—GSB (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - May 23, 1988 National Major Gifts Co-Chairs Meeting Materials (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Major Gifts Co-Chairs (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Final Campaign Reports (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Major Gifts Co-Chairs (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Major Gifts Co-Chairs (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Major Gifts Program (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - May 8, 1986—NMGC Co-Chairs Dinner Meeting 5:30-7:00ish (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Report by Objectives (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Centennial ‘100' (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee Meeting 1/7/91 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee Meetings (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Campaign June 27, 1986 Campaign Steering Committee Meeting (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Campaign Faculty/Staff Solicitations (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Campaign, Campaign Co-Chairs Newsletter (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Names (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Campaign Co-Chairs Luncheons (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Campaign Steering Committee 10/31/91 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Steering Committee 10-31-91 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Co-Chairs 8-1-91 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Trustees 2/11/91 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Steering Committee Meeting January 7, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Steering Committee 1-7-91 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Trustees Retreat 9-7-90 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Co-Chairs Meeting—Phoenix, Arizona April 6, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Co-Chairs 4-6-90 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Steering Committee Meeting February 13, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Trustees 2-2-90 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Steering Committee 2-13-90 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Steering Committee Meeting February 13, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Senate 2-8-90 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Co-Chairs Meeting January 9, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Co-Chairs 1-9-90 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Co-Chairs Meeting November 18, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Co-Chairs 11-18-89 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Steering Committee Meeting October 11, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Steering Committee Meeting 10-11-89 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Campaign Steering Committee Mtg. Oct. 11, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Co-Chairs 7-26-89 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Co-Chairs Meeting July 26, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Trustees 2-14-89 St. Comm 2-15-89 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Steering Committee Meeting February 14, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Co-Chairs 1-23-89 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Co-Chairs Meeting January 23, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Co-Chairs 11/18/88 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - St. Comm 10/12/88 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Steering Committee 10/12/88 Overheads for John Ford (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Campaign Chairs (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Resource Group (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Campaign Objectives Fine Arts (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Gift Opportunities (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Campaign—Foundations/Corporations 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Chris Connell (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Faculty Staff Solicitation (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Keystone Steering Comm. (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Annual Fund (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Campaign Planning (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Centennial Bench (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Assorted Memos, Reports (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Campaign Press Coverage (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Plan Elements (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Campaign—Communications 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Press Coverage (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Office of the President and Office of the Provost Centennial Campaign Fundraising Goals February 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Earth Sciences Centennial (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Objectives Professorships (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - DAPER and the Centennial Campaign (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Dinner Dance 11/10/1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Campaign—Events/Kick-off (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Campaign Featured Objectives Revised Jan. 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Campaign Burr Gibson conversations (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Campaign Don Kennedy Lunches Feb/Mar 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Centennial Campaign Matching Provisions (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Centennial Campaign Mid-Campaign Events (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Campaign National Centennial Celebrations (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - L/G Steinberg Mr. Ralph J. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Medallion Awards (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Centennial Campaign Near West Campus (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Campaign News (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Centennial—Nucleus Fund—Trustee Solicitation (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Plan 1977, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Centennial Program Plans for Foundation & Corporation Relations (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Program Plan Corporate/Foundation Program Centennial Campaign (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Centennial Press (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Background Memos (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Burr Gibson (Box 28, Folder Folder27)
    - Revised End $ and Revised Featured Objectives (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Volunteer Solicitation (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Trustee Solicitation (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Centennial Planning Committee (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Ivy Trips re: Centennial (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Major Gifts/Sources (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Names for the Campaign (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Press Conferences & Publicity (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Keystone Reporting System (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - PFCCC (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Campaign Staff Newsletters (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Senate Committee (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Centennial Annual Fund Marketing Statistics Preliminary Report December 1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Changes to table 121 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Athletics and Recreation Intramural and Recreation Facilities (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Christopher Lovelock Study (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Annual Fund Donor Study (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Fulner Report—future value of new donor (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Campaign Progress Rpt Working Papers (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Progress Reports revised format April 1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Centennial Campaign: Policies (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Campaign: Prospectus (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Comments on Prospectus Draft of 10.7.85 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Centennial Campaign Solicitation Target (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Retreat Materials (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - February 6, 1992 South Bay Major Gifts Council Meeting (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - South Bay Development—History & General Fundraising Information (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - South Bay Council Meeting—March 28 and April 4, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - JC letters (chron) (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - President's Centennial Discussion Final Report 1986 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Presidential Centennial Events Centennial Campaign 1985/86 SRA (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Campaign Volunteer Training (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Training Meeting—Wednesday, May 13—Room 13 History Corner 9:30 a.m. to 11:30 a.m. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - President's Centennial Discussion—Final Report (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - President's Centennial Discussion (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - L/G President's Discussion—Budget (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - L/G President's Centennial Discussion Presidential Letter of Thanks to Attendees (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Second Round PCD Events (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - L/G—PCD "The Prospectus as a Campaign Tool" Meetings (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - L/G Presidential Dinners (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Planning Comm. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 2:00 p.m. Meeting with Stearns and Farrell (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Featured Objectives "Price List" (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Task Force—Misc. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - CTF Meeting w Bacchetti 12-7-82 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Annual Fund Committees (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Centennial—Nucleus Fund (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Campaign: Nucleus Fund (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Nucleus Fund (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Watson Stanford Golf Day (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Watson 1995 Event (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Centennial Committee (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - "Centennial Celebration" (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - WFD Centennial Campaign (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Centennial Campaign Campaign Case Statement Mailings (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Centennial Campaign #2 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Watson @ Spanish Bay (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Tom Watson @ Spanish Bay (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Watson (Monterey Bay Aquarium) (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Watson (Seminar Speaker) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Campaign Totals (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - WFD Centennial Dinner (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The Stanford Centennial Campaign (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Plans 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Prospecting Program 1982-84 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Prospecting (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Venture Capital (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Binders
      - Final Campaign Report by School 1992 (Box 31)
      - Presidential Centennial Discussions 1986 (Box 31)
      - Centennial Campaign 1985-1986 (Box 32)
      - Centennial Campaign Fundraising Reports 1987-92 (Box 32)
      - Centennial Campaign Program Planning 1986 (Box 32)
      - President's Centennial Discussions Final Report for Staff Use October 1986 (Box 32)
      - Princeton Campaign Master Plan Notebook 1981 (Box 32)
  - PACE Campaign
    - PACE Staff Retreat 3/24/64 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Binders
      - Long Range Planning 1964 (Box 32)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2008-239
  - Evaluation Reports Stanford PACE Program 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Stanford, Sept. 29, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Development Office Task Force on Centennial Fundraising, April 29, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Campaign Plans (1 of 3) 1984-87 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Campaign Plans (2 of 3) 1984-87 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Campaign Plans (3 of 3) 1984-87 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - President's Centennial Discussions. Final Report for Staff Use, October 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Major Gifts Co-Chairs Meeting, Feb. 9, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Campaign Regional Totals 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Silicon Valley Task Force Progress Report 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Undergraduate Education. Campaign Plan 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Challenge. Stanford University Volunteer Convocation Media Piece, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 2.3U)
  - Stanford Challenge [five short videos showing the Stanford Challenge in action], 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 2.4U)
  - Ivy MIT Stanford conference, schedule and information, Sept. 10-11, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - September 11, 2001: emails, Tim Portwood's account of the NYC after the attacks, the drive from NYC back to California, and postcards from states along the route (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - SEQ II, Boora Hargreaves Associates: PowerPoint presentation, June 2, 2004; 1 computer file(s) (ppt) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Video Annual Report, 2004-05; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 2.8U)
  - Jim Gaither, Uncommon Man Award, photographs by Steve Castillo, 2006; 110 computer file(s) (jpg)
  - School of Medicine Centennial Dinner invitation, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Fairchild Era; Three Decades of Collaboration and Discovery at Stanford University School of Medicine; produced for the Sherman Fairchild Foundation, January 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIALS:
    - Development Priorities Committee agenda and minutes, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Campaign reports, statistics, memos, etc. 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Campaign 1992 Status Report (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - FRANual materials (Box 4)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2009-192
  - Mr. Executive: Higher education is your business [fundraising publication (15x11 inches) circa 1955]. This item was removed from its mildewed leather portfolio. (Box 1)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2010-037
  - Ad Hoc committee on Campaign Planning (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SUH [Hospital] Replacement (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Woods Institute Advisory Council meeting (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Initiative (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Global Climate & Energy Project [GCEP] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Science, Engineering, and Medical Campus [SECM] Plan (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Science, Engineering, and Medical Campus [SECM] Plan (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Housing (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Performing Arts Center - Bing (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Performing Arts Center planning (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Performing Arts Center (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts Initiative (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Hospitals and Clinics, Committee meeting packets (Development, Nominations and Governance, Community Relations) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Challenge Matching program (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer Convocation (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive / Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Executive / Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Campaign Executive Committee [cancelled] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Executive / Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Campaign Executive Committee, Deer Valley Retreat (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Executive Committee, Conference Call (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Campaign Executive Committee, Conference Call (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Executive Committee, Confernce Call (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Campaign Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Campaign Executive Committee miscellany (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Campaign Volunteer Organization (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - University Campaign (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - University Campaign - Draft (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - University Campaign. memoranda, email, etc. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Executive committee (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DMG Planning Reports (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Teaching Initiative (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - CUE Volume I (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - CUE Volume III (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CUE Volume III (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Don Kennedy Professorship (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gregg Project (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Board Reports I (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Board Reports II (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Board Reports III (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Board - reviews and plans (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 3-Year Budget Plan 1991/92 - 1993/94 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SU Budget Reduction Plan (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Final Report of the Office of Development Long Range Planning Committee Nov. 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Final Report of the Office of Development Long Range Planning Committee Nov. 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Office of Development Budget (Box 2, Folder 43)
- The Charles and Nancy Munger Graduate Residence at Stanford University. Stewardship piece [printed volume of photographs and text] presented to Charles Munger, 2010-08; Accession ARCH-2010-095 (Box 1)
- Audiovisual material, 1988-2013; Accession ARCH-2015-136
  - Thing Again National Tour 2001-2002 Film from Think Again Stanford University, A67; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - George Shultz, 2006-02-12; A68; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Pres/parents Weekend Disc 2 audio, 2006-02-22; A69; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - A Stanford Salute to Justice Sandra Day O'Connor '50, LLB '52 Brought to you by: the Washington, D.C. Stanford Association, the Stanford Law Society of Washington D.C., the Stanford Alumni Association, and the Stanford Law School, 2006-06-23; A70; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Anxious Times Seeing Beyond a World of Perpetual Threats Roundtable Discussion, 2006-10-14; A71; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Y2E2 Building Reception, 2007-07-21; A72; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - John Ford Retirement Reception Stanford Faculty Club Disc 1, 2008-01-29; A73; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - John Ford Retirement Reception Stanford Faculty Club Disc 2, 2008-01-29; A74; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - John & Jill Friedenrich Award Photos Steve Castillo, 2010-12-10; A77; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Li Ka Shing Center Dedication, 2010-12-29; A78; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Li Ka Shing Center Dedication, 2010-12-29; A79; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Jim Gaither Uncommon Man Videos, 2013-06-08; A84; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - Windhover Groundbreak Photos by David Gonzales, 2013-06-24; A85; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)